volt.com 2019-08-28

# Volt Information Sciences, Inc. Privacy Policy

                                 Volt Information Sciences, Inc. Privacy Policy
                                                Effective Date: May 10, 2019
This Privacy Policy discloses practices for collection, use and protection of your personal information by Volt
Information Sciences, Inc. and its subsidiaries, affiliates, and divisions (hereinafter collectively the “Company”).
The Company operates in accordance with the EU Data Protection Directives 95/46/EC and 2002/58/EC as
amended and updated (the “Directives”) as appropriate to the jurisdiction in which Company is trading.
Personal Information the Company Collects
In the course of its business, the Company collects personal information, which was given to or made
available to the Company for an intended business function or purpose. The information may include a
name combined with a unique identification number, including a social security and/or national identification
number, home address, mailing address, e-mail address, social media identifier, driver’s license number,
birthdate, country location, personal home, or cell/mobile telephone number(s), historical work or education
information, compensation/benefits/pay rates, bank account information, pricing, medical or claims
information and/or performance data (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Personal Information”).
Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information
Personal Information is used in connection with the Company’s business, including providing recruitment,
placement, and employment services to our employment candidates, employees, customers and for other
lawful purposes.
The Company does not disclose Personal Information except in the following instances:
 • With the subsidiaries and affiliates within the Company, as needed;
 • With your express consent;
 • Where permitted and/or required by our customer/client agreements, including for billing purposes;
 • To facilitate job opportunities for our candidates;
 • With third party entities, vendors, consultants, agents and/or other service providers engaged to handle
      or manage some or all of the Personal Information on our behalf, who shall be required to protect
      Personal Information from dissemination and/or use;
 • When we believe disclosure is appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss and/or when
      reasonably necessary to an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activities;
 • When required and/or otherwise permitted by law;
 • In response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement
      requirements;
 • If you are a customer/client, the Company may share information with third parties, such as with a credit
      bureau or agency; and
 • In connection with any merger, sale of Company assets or acquisition of all or a portion of the
      Company’s business or with respect to any Company financing.
Data Processing Outside Your Country
We may transfer your information and process it outside your country of residence to wherever Company or our
clients or our third party data processors operate.
                                                              1

Privacy Shield
With respect to Personal Information associated with individuals located in European Economic Area (EEA)
countries (“EEA Data Subjects”), the Company complies with the Data Protection Directive 95/46/ec as
amended. For a list of the U.S. subsidiaries that adhere to the Privacy Shield principles, please reference our
Privacy Shield registration at https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.
To the extent that Personal Information of EEA Data Subjects is transferred to the United States of America,
the Company complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of
Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information transferred from the EEA to
the United States. The Company remains responsible for personal information that is shared under the
Onward Transfer Principle with third parties for external processing on Company’s behalf.
The Company has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If
there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield
Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please
visit www.privacyshield.gov.
 Notice of material changes to the use or transfer of your Personal Information incompatible with the
 purpose for which it was originally collected will be provided through our website or by other means so that
 you may review the changes before you continue your relationship with the Company. If you object to the
 changes, you must notify of us of your wish to sever your relationship with the Company; otherwise, your
 continuance of the relationship after the notice means that you are consenting to the changes.
 The Company is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission to
 ensure compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield principles outlined in this Privacy Policy.
 In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, the Company commits to resolve complaints about your
 privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. JAMS will be the US-based independent
 organization responsible for reviewing and resolving complaints about our Privacy Shield compliance. We ask
 that you first submit any such complaints directly to us via Privacy@volt.com. If you are not satisfied with our
 response, please contact JAMS at https://jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield. In the event your concern still is
 not addressed by JAMS, you may be entitled to a binding arbitration under Privacy Shield and its principles.
 The Company commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice
 given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the
 employment relationship.
Solicitations and/or Marketing Contacts
The Company does not sell, convey and/or communicate customer/client, business associate, supplier,
vendor, employee and/or candidate Personal Information to third parties for purposes of direct mail,
telemarketing, and/or related promotions, solicitations or marketing contacts.
                                                          2

Management of Personal Information
The Company uses a combination of reasonable security technologies, policies and procedures, and non-
disclosure, confidentiality and/or other forms of agreement(s) to help protect your Personal Information
from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.In the event that local law in the
country of disclosure or use of Personal Information is more stringent than the requirements set out in
this policy, local law will prevail over this policy to the extent necessary to meet the requirements of that
legislation.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
The Company, in its sole and absolute discretion, reserves the right to supersede, modify, supplement,
replace or eliminate this Policy, which shall be effective upon publication on the Company’s website.
Requests to access and to make changes in Personal Information
In the event that any individual wishes to access, change, correct or delete Personal Information and its
treatment as covered by this Privacy Policy, he or she must submit a written request to privacy@volt.com.
You have the right to request that usage or disclosure of your information be limited, however such usage
of your information as described above may be necessary for the performance of recruitment,
placement, and employment services that we provide to you. As such, a request to withdraw consent,
object to processing, limit usage or erase your information may result in Volt being unable to continue
providing its services such as recruitment, placement or employment services.
Who to Contact About this Privacy Policy
Any questions or complaints regarding the Company’s Privacy Policy should be directed to:
Volt Information Sciences, Inc.
959 Route 46 East, Suite 201
Parsippany, NJ 07054
Attn: Vice President Risk Management
Privacy@volt.com
                                                          3
